Lloyd: So now that you've completed
session two of unit six, it's
time to compete the relevant
section in the assessment booklet.
So if you open your assessment booklet
and scroll down to section two, this
is Understand the Use of Interpersonal
Skills for Working in Cyber Security.
So there are three learning objectives in
this section and three questions to allow
you to fulfill those learning objectives.
So for question one, it's asking
you to identify a range of
interpersonal skills that you use
when working in cyber security.
The question asks specifically for cyber
security, but I think interpersonal
skills are applicable in all working
roles and in all aspects of life.
So what are the sort of interpersonal
skills that you could utilise effectively
when working in cyber security?
So if you've worked in a team,
what are the interpersonal skills
that you use and think about the
ones that may be more applicable
in a cyber security environment.
For question two, it's asked you to
give three examples of when different
interpersonal skills might be used
when working in cyber security.
So again, you can think about what you've
suggested for your answer to question
one and then give three examples.
So think about them in
relation to cyber security.
So what would be the benefit
of those in cyber security?
So once you've given the three
examples for there, for question
three, it's asking you to describe
how working with others within an
organisation can support cyber security.
So what is it that you can
do when you're working with
others within an organisation?
This doesn't necessarily mean people
who are working in cyber security,
it can just be a case of people who
are working within an organisation.
What can you all do?
And working with others to ensure
cyber security needs are met and cyber
security is with it being a critical
component of any organisation, what can
you do to ensure that you are supporting
cyber security within the workplace?
So once you've done that, if you
read through your answers, carry
out a spelling and grammar check,
and then you can save your unit six
assessment and move on to session three.